(Love is)
(الحب هو)
(something sweet between a couple.)
(شيء حلو بين زوجين).
(But the love of him and me)
(لكن حبه لي وحبي)
(turns out)
(يتحول)
(to be a "love triangle of two".)
(ليكون "مثلث الحب لاثنين".)
Su Ziying?
سو زيينغ؟
(It's full of unknowns)
(إنها مليئة بالمجهول)
(and crises.)
(والأزمات).
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
Ye Juncheng.
يي جونتشنغ.
=EP24 I Just Love You=
= EP24 أنا أحبك فقط =
Hey, hey.
مرحبًا.
He's waking up.
إنه يستيقظ.
Look, he woke up.
انظر ، استيقظ.
He's awake now.
إنه مستيقظ الآن.
I'm not dead.
انا لست ميت.
Why the long face?
لماذا الوجه الطويل؟
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
you'd better not die.
من الأفضل ألا تموت.
Or who will pay me?
أو من سيدفع لي؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You should pay her first.
يجب أن تدفع لها أولاً.
Be quiet.
كن هادئاً.
We'll leave you alone.
سنتركك وشأنك.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Are we having a long-distance relationship?
هل لدينا علاقة طويلة المدى؟
We have to always keep a safe distance.
يجب أن نحافظ دائمًا على مسافة آمنة.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I asked the doctor.
سألت الطبيب.
Split personality is
انقسام الشخصية
a mental disease.
مرض عقلي.
It should be treated as early as possible.
يجب معالجته في أقرب وقت ممكن.
But...
ولكن...
I'm worried
انا قلق
that I'm not the guy
أنني لست الرجل
who can stay in the end.
من يستطيع البقاء في النهاية.
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
you're just too stubborn
أنت فقط عنيد جدا
and you deserve it.
وأنت تستحقها.
Every time I touch you,
في كل مرة ألمسك
you'll have an exchanged personality, huh?
سيكون لديك شخصية متبادلة ، أليس كذلك؟
Then I can always keep a safe distance.
ثم يمكنني دائمًا الحفاظ على مسافة آمنة.
I won't touch you,
لن ألمسك
or hug you.
أو أحضنك.
I'll always stay with you
سأبقى دائما معك
and never leave you.
ولا اتركك ابدا.
(Dissociative Identity Disorder)
(اضطراب الهوية الانفصامية)
(Enneagram)
(إنيغرام)
(Redefinition of Enneagram)
(إعادة تعريف Enneagram)
Hello,
مرحبًا،
Lin Han.
لين هان.
Could you do me a favor?
هل من الممكن ان تصنع لي معروفآ؟
You should tell her as early as possible.
يجب أن تخبرها في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Otherwise...
خلاف ذلك...
We should make it quick.
يجب أن نجعلها سريعة.
I know...
أنا أعرف...
Hey, Ziying.
مرحبًا ، Ziying.
Su Ziying, what's your plan for today?
سو زيينغ ، ما هي خطتك لهذا اليوم؟
How about I take you out for fun?
ماذا لو أخرجك من أجل المتعة؟
I've found many books about Dissociative Identity Disorder.
لقد وجدت العديد من الكتب حول اضطراب الهوية الانفصامية.
I'm on my way to see Ye Juncheng.
أنا في طريقي لرؤية يي جونتشنغ.
Don't. Don't.
لا.  لا.
You haven't had fun with us for a long time.
لم تستمتع معنا منذ فترة طويلة.
I booked a KTV room.
حجزت غرفة KTV.
We can have lunch
يمكننا تناول الغداء
and sing songs together...
ونغني الأغاني معًا ...
I really have something to do.
أنا حقا لدي شيء لأفعله.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
If you don't want to sing, okay.
إذا كنت لا تريد الغناء ، حسنًا.
Right.
الصحيح.
Let's do some homework.
لنقم ببعض الواجبات المنزلية.
- Go skiing. - Or doing some coaching.
- اذهب للتزلج.  - أو القيام ببعض التدريب.
You always want to ski, right?
تريد دائمًا التزلج ، أليس كذلك؟
- Come on. What on earth are you doing? - Yeah. No matter what you want...
- هيا.  ماذا تفعل بحق الارض؟  - نعم.  لا يهم ما تريد ...
What exactly happened?
ماذا حدث بالضبط؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Ye...
انتم ...
Ye Juncheng
يي جونتشنغ
has gone to see
ذهب ليرى
a psycholo...
نفساني ...
Wait, Ziying.
انتظر ، تسيينغ.
♪Reality is♪
♪ الواقع هو ♪
♪Harder than we imagined♪
♪ أصعب مما تخيلنا ♪
♪With twists and turns♪
♪ مع التقلبات والانعطافات ♪
♪This is where we have to stop♪
♪ هذا هو المكان الذي يجب أن نتوقف فيه ♪
Ye Juncheng.
يي جونتشنغ.
♪If♪
♪ إذا
♪If we could be braver♪
♪ إذا استطعنا أن نكون أكثر شجاعة
♪We would♪
♪ نود ♪
(Boy,)
(ولد،)
(listen.)
(استمع.)
(I've decided to accept the treatment.)
(قررت قبول العلاج).
(Whether you or I stay,)
(سواء كنت أنت أو بقيت ،)
(remember)
(تذكر)
(to be nice to Su Ziying.)
(ليكون لطيفًا مع Su Ziying.)
(She appears to be very strong,)
(يبدو أنها قوية جدًا ،)
(but she's actually fragile.)
(لكنها في الواقع هشة).
(She loves money,)
(تحب المال)
(because she has to take care of her grandma.)
(لأنها يجب أن تعتني بجدتها).
(She's tough,)
(إنها صعبة ،)
(so she does everything very well.)
(لذا فهي تفعل كل شيء جيدًا.)
♪I still love you♪
♪ ما زلت أحبك
During the outbreak of COVID-19, please keep your distance.
أثناء تفشي وباء كوفيد -19 ، يرجى الابتعاد عنك.
♪Until we make our choices♪
حتى نقوم باختياراتنا ♪
8.8 yuan?
8.8 يوان؟
You asked me to pay as much as I wanted.
طلبت مني أن أدفع قدر ما أريد.
You can't be afraid of the dark, can you?
لا يمكنك أن تخاف من الظلام ، أليس كذلك؟
♪Don't let it happen again♪
♪ لا تدع ذلك يحدث مرة أخرى
♪What you regret♪
ما تندم عليه ♪
♪Goes on again and again♪
يمضي مرارًا وتكرارًا
♪Repeating the assumptions♪
تكرار الافتراضات ♪
Tell me what you want.
قل لي ماذا تريد.
Under what circumstances would you be my girlfriend?
تحت أي ظروف ستكون صديقتي؟
Or that you can't help touching me?
أو أنك لا تستطيع المساعدة في لمسي؟
♪There's no if in life When you want something♪
♪ لا يوجد إذا في الحياة عندما تريد شيئًا ♪
♪Hold it tight♪
♪ امسكها بقوة ♪
Ye Juncheng.
يي جونتشنغ.
I won't leave you again, Ziying.
لن أتركك مرة أخرى ، Ziying.
Sorry.
آسف.
I have something offensive to say.
لدي شيء مسيء لأقوله.
But don't take it personally.
لكن لا تأخذ الأمر على محمل شخصي.
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
you are
أنت
a playboy,
مستهتر
miser,
البخيل،
and ruffian!
ورافيان!
I thought I would never get rid of such an annoying guy like you.
اعتقدت أنني لن أتخلص من مثل هذا الرجل المزعج مثلك.
But,
ولكن،
why are you just gone?
لماذا ذهبت للتو
You...
أنت...
Am I really this bad?
هل أنا حقا بهذا السوء؟
My senior,
زميلي القديم،
I'll pay you 8.8 yuan.
سأدفع لك 8.8 يوان.
Get changed
تغير
and be my model,
وكوني نموذجي ،
will you?
سوف تفعل؟
(Some people seemed)
(بدا بعض الناس)
(to meet each other by accident.)
(لمقابلة بعضنا البعض عن طريق الصدفة.)
(But actually,)
(لكن في الواقع ،)
(the ending was arranged)
(تم ترتيب النهاية)
(before anybody knew that,)
(قبل أن يعرف أحد ذلك ،)
(with even)
(مع زوجي)
(a particular mission.)
(مهمة معينة.)
♪You're so perfect my love my love♪
♪ أنت مثالي جدًا حبيبي
♪You hug me and get no longer defensive♪
أنت تعانقني ولم تعد دفاعيًا ♪
(In love, if you insist on something,)
(في الحب ، إذا أصررت على شيء ،)
(you'll get it.)
(ستحصل عليها او عليه.)
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
your illness has recovered, huh?
مرضك قد تعافى ، أليس كذلك؟
But mine hasn't yet.
لكني لم تفعل ذلك بعد.
♪My love my love♪
♪ حبيبي حبي ♪
♪You lay claim to my heart♪
أنت تطالب بقلبي ♪
I just won't let him out.
أنا فقط لن أسمح له بالخروج.
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
♪There's no if in life When you want something♪
♪ لا يوجد إذا في الحياة عندما تريد شيئًا ♪
♪Hold it tight♪
♪ امسكها بقوة ♪
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)